Hyper Oragonic attack!
Got him good
And so, thanks to hero Oragon
Monster world has been saved
As you can see
I was the leader of our popular heroes
Because I played such an important role
Heres a surprise announcement of my goods!
In addition, only now,
buy one and get extra three!
Now that's a bargain
But still..
I think I made too much of it
Oh?
Someone already wants to order?
Its not a lie!
We're close friends with Lucifer
Ah!
I don't have any photos for proof, but
Tree of the Future that I received
Should be somewhere in the room
Hmm? Where was it again?
Weird
Ah!
Don't point it that way!
Theres a veeeery good explanation for this
Everyone, please wait!
I might have went too far with my story
But we really saved Monster world
We worked so hard
Why won't you believe me
This is...
Not this again!
This is bad
Ow ow ow
That could not have been any worse
Oragon!
Hmm? This voice.. If I'm right..
Ah, there you are
As I thought, it was you Oranee
Hows the Tree of Future that I gave you doing!?
Hah!?
The tree that shows the future of Strike World!
Gulp!
Of course, it has to be pretty healthy, right?
Yes yes, very healthy
Blossomed..
Blossomed so much that it almost feels like Spring
Hmm?
Was this the only reason you summoned be here?
If the tree is doing fine
Then the future of Strike World should have also been safe
It started!
Fireworks?
Oh?
Wait for me Oranee!
You'll have to re-pay me for destroyed goods!
Hmm, seems to be pretty hectic out here
Oh no
They really are attacking
This voice..
Please, calm down
Everyone, head down to the palace
Solomon!
Everything is going to be alright!
Its the Solomon!
Oragon!
Are you alright?
Is this, by chance..?
An all out attack!?
Levi-sama!
At this rate, if they continue the attack, the barrier
I know!
We cant pull any more power from the Master orb!
Solomon-chan!
Leave this for us!
But
Solomon
You should join the soldiers
Will do, thanks
Watch out, Oragon!
This way!
That was really close
Why did you suddenly rush forward!?
To ensure the safety of my goods
Forget about that, we need to evacuate
Unforgivable!
Huh!?
After we saved the world with Lucifer
Who's the one cause the ruckus here??
Listen, it might be surprising, but its..
Take this! A royal gift from this proud monarch!
Surgat, that's enough
Zephon, already here?
Yes
Well well, took all the fun
Droz!
Lucifer!
Why are doing it like this?
Don't stay silent, answer me!
Stop right there, Lucifer!
Odarot!
Defeat the enemy!
This is a sacred place
If you want to go any further
I will show no mercy!
This flame
Can't be
Hey Solomon
Caesar!?
Why are you here?
Theres need for you to know that
Odarot!
You should be safe over here
Okay, lets return back to Solomon
Until the fight is over, please stay hidden
Hey, so what is Lucifer trying to achieve?
If its to destroy Lecillia, then..
This light!
They're finally here
Noah!
Returning back from Strike field
Noah, switching back to main monitor
Please do
Can't be believe, It's already happening!?
Opeko, please inform Arthur and Pandora
Okay!
Are you two ready to go out?
Binah!
Are you alright?
Yes
What about Solomon?
Must be heading towards the palace
Lets go!
Mhm!
Mopey-kun, lets go
Bihan, wait for us in the ship
Odarot!
*magic spell*!
Too bad!
Trying to get an upper hand with the Holy King spells is..
Hmm?
Is it already time to end this?
Thought you could entertain me a bit more
Seems that my expectations were wrong
The throne!?
I like that
That was a pretty good execution
Now then,
Lets continue
But don't break too fast for me
Wh.. Why is Lucifer..?
Do you believe me now?
We should evacuate out of here
Ah!
They're here!
Everyone managed to arrive in time
It's Noah's Arc!
Have to keep going
Drez Ekir!
That explosion just now
If I'm right, it one of Solomon's friends
Leave her to me
Thanks!
Will take care of Lucifer then!
Agreed!
Arthur!
I'm alright!
Here they come!
Paeni Entia
O' Light
Pour down!
Damn it!
Noah!
Not a time for you to worry about others
Ah!
There you are!
Hey hey! Are you alright?
Mopey-kun, we're bringing her back to the ship
Don't move
Don't want to die yet, right?
Hey! It reached from all the way back there!?
Forneus?
Oi!
Oh no!
Caught you!
Royal Palace!
Lucifer, you're really going this far
Ah, someone is approaching
Isn't that Oranee?
This has to be some kind of misunderstanding
You're still talking about that?
Come on, this way
Heeeyy!
We have to go now
Seems that she managed to get it
Odarot!
Play time is over
Lets leave before we get dragged into
Everyone, I'm going to prepare
Please do
What is happening!?
Because Lucifer has stolen the Master Orb
Lecillia is starting to collapse
Eeehh!?
Collapse? What do you mean?
You know how each Strike world has its own guardian?
Master orb connects each world with its energy
In case the orb is stolen from that world
Its going to eventually be destroyed
What!?
Your name was Noah, right?
Time flew by while playing with you
Will have to excuse myself now
Wait!
What are these?
What is happening?
If you don't want to die
You should run from this world
What?
I've warned you
W..Wait!
Arthur!
Grab my hand
Opeko, time to evacuate
Pick us up
Okay
Everyone, listen
The collapse has started
We have to hurry to pick up everyone
Noah has contacted me
But theres still Solomon and Pandora
Ah! There she is! Pandora is here
She's heading this way
Thank god, she's safe
Pandora, are you alright?
Yes, more importantly, this girl
Badly hurt
It can't be
Is that Levy-chan?